[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Who won the FIFA World Cup in 2022?",
        "options": [
            "Argentina",
            "France",
            "Brazil",
            "Germany"
        ],
        "answer": "Argentina"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Who is known as CR7?",
        "options": [
            "Messi",
            "Neymar",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Mbappé"
        ],
        "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which country has won the most FIFA World Cups?",
        "options": [
            "Germany",
            "Brazil",
            "Italy",
            "Argentina"
        ],
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which club does Lionel Messi currently play for?",
        "options": [
            "Barcelona",
            "PSG",
            "Manchester City",
            "Inter Miami"
        ],
        "answer": "Inter Miami"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "How many players are on the field for each team?",
        "options": [
            "11",
            "10",
            "12",
            "9"
        ],
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which country hosted the 2018 FIFA World Cup?",
        "options": [
            "Germany",
            "Russia",
            "Brazil",
            "Qatar"
        ],
        "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which player has the most Ballon d'Or awards?",
        "options": [
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Modric",
            "Ronaldinho"
        ],
        "answer": "Lionel Messi"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Maximum duration of a standard football match?",
        "options": [
            "70 min",
            "100 min",
            "80 min",
            "90 min"
        ],
        "answer": "90 min"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Who won UEFA Champions League in 2023?",
        "options": [
            "Manchester City",
            "Real Madrid",
            "Liverpool",
            "Bayern Munich"
        ],
        "answer": "Manchester City"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which position wears the number 1 jersey?",
        "options": [
            "Striker",
            "Midfielder",
            "Goalkeeper",
            "Defender"
        ],
        "answer": "Goalkeeper"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Which country won the first FIFA World Cup in 1930?",
        "options": [
            "Argentina",
            "Uruguay",
            "Brazil",
            "Italy"
        ],
        "answer": "Uruguay"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer in World Cup history?",
        "options": [
            "Ronaldo",
            "Pelé",
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Miroslav Klose"
        ],
        "answer": "Miroslav Klose"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Which club is nicknamed 'Red Devils'?",
        "options": [
            "Manchester United",
            "Liverpool",
            "Arsenal",
            "Chelsea"
        ],
        "answer": "Manchester United"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Which country won Euro 2020?",
        "options": [
            "Spain",
            "Italy",
            "England",
            "France"
        ],
        "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Who won the Golden Boot in FIFA World Cup 2018?",
        "options": [
            "Mbappé",
            "Harry Kane",
            "Messi",
            "Lukaku"
        ],
        "answer": "Harry Kane"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "Which club won the 2023 English Premier League?",
        "options": [
            "Arsenal",
            "Chelsea",
            "Liverpool",
            "Manchester City"
        ],
        "answer": "Manchester City"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "Which country has Lionel Messi represented internationally?",
        "options": [
            "Argentina",
            "Brazil",
            "Spain",
            "Portugal"
        ],
        "answer": "Argentina"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "Which footballer is known as 'King of Football'?",
        "options": [
            "Messi",
            "Ronaldo",
            "Pele",
            "Maradona"
        ],
        "answer": "Pele"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "Which country won the Copa America 2021?",
        "options": [
            "Uruguay",
            "Argentina",
            "Brazil",
            "Chile"
        ],
        "answer": "Argentina"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "Who won UEFA Champions League in 2022?",
        "options": [
            "Chelsea",
            "Liverpool",
            "Manchester City",
            "Real Madrid"
        ],
        "answer": "Real Madrid"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "Which country hosted the 2006 FIFA World Cup?",
        "options": [
            "Germany",
            "Italy",
            "France",
            "Brazil"
        ],
        "answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "Which player scored the 'Hand of God' goal?",
        "options": [
            "Messi",
            "Maradona",
            "Pelé",
            "Ronaldo"
        ],
        "answer": "Maradona"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "Which club has the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
        "options": [
            "AC Milan",
            "Real Madrid",
            "Liverpool",
            "Barcelona"
        ],
        "answer": "Real Madrid"
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "Who won the Ballon d'Or in 2021?",
        "options": [
            "Ronaldo",
            "Mbappé",
            "Lewandowski",
            "Messi"
        ],
        "answer": "Lionel Messi"
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "Which country has the nickname 'Three Lions'?",
        "options": [
            "England",
            "France",
            "Italy",
            "Germany"
        ],
        "answer": "England"
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "Which footballer is nicknamed 'The Pharaoh'?",
        "options": [
            "Riyad Mahrez",
            "Mohamed Salah",
            "Hakimi",
            "Sadio Mané"
        ],
        "answer": "Mohamed Salah"
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "Which country won the FIFA World Cup in 1998?",
        "options": [
            "Brazil",
            "France",
            "Italy",
            "Germany"
        ],
        "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "Which club is called 'The Old Lady'?",
        "options": [
            "AC Milan",
            "Napoli",
            "Inter Milan",
            "Juventus"
        ],
        "answer": "Juventus"
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer for Barcelona?",
        "options": [
            "Messi",
            "Suárez",
            "Neymar",
            "Ronaldinho"
        ],
        "answer": "Messi"
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "Which country won the Euro 2016?",
        "options": [
            "France",
            "Portugal",
            "Germany",
            "Spain"
        ],
        "answer": "Portugal"
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "Which goalkeeper won the Ballon d'Or in 1963?",
        "options": [
            "Gianluigi Buffon",
            "Lev Yashin",
            "Iker Casillas",
            "Peter Schmeichel"
        ],
        "answer": "Lev Yashin"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "Which club is nicknamed 'The Citizens'?",
        "options": [
            "Liverpool",
            "Manchester United",
            "Chelsea",
            "Manchester City"
        ],
        "answer": "Manchester City"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "Who won the FIFA World Cup Golden Ball in 2018?",
        "options": [
            "Luka Modric",
            "Mbappé",
            "Ronaldo",
            "Messi"
        ],
        "answer": "Luka Modric"
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "Which country won Copa America 2019?",
        "options": [
            "Argentina",
            "Brazil",
            "Chile",
            "Uruguay"
        ],
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "Which country has the nickname 'Socceroos'?",
        "options": [
            "New Zealand",
            "Australia",
            "South Africa",
            "England"
        ],
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "Which player scored 5 goals in a single World Cup match?",
        "options": [
            "Miroslav Klose",
            "Ronaldo",
            "Pelé",
            "Oleg Salenko"
        ],
        "answer": "Oleg Salenko"
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "Which country won the first ever European Championship in 1960?",
        "options": [
            "Soviet Union",
            "France",
            "Italy",
            "Spain"
        ],
        "answer": "Soviet Union"
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "Which club won the UEFA Europa League in 2021?",
        "options": [
            "Villarreal",
            "Sevilla",
            "Manchester United",
            "Arsenal"
        ],
        "answer": "Villarreal"
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "Which country won the 2002 FIFA World Cup?",
        "options": [
            "Germany",
            "Brazil",
            "Turkey",
            "South Korea"
        ],
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "Which player is known as 'The Egyptian King'?",
        "options": [
            "Riyad Mahrez",
            "Hakimi",
            "Salah Abou",
            "Mohamed Salah"
        ],
        "answer": "Mohamed Salah"
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "Which club won the 2022–23 La Liga title?",
        "options": [
            "Barcelona",
            "Real Madrid",
            "Atletico Madrid",
            "Sevilla"
        ],
        "answer": "Barcelona"
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "Which country won the FIFA Confederations Cup in 2017?",
        "options": [
            "Chile",
            "Germany",
            "Argentina",
            "Brazil"
        ],
        "answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "Which footballer is called 'The Atomic Flea'?",
        "options": [
            "Messi",
            "Neymar",
            "Mbappé",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo"
        ],
        "answer": "Messi"
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "Which club won the English FA Cup in 2022?",
        "options": [
            "Arsenal",
            "Manchester City",
            "Liverpool",
            "Chelsea"
        ],
        "answer": "Liverpool"
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "Which country won FIFA U-17 World Cup in 2019?",
        "options": [
            "Brazil",
            "Mexico",
            "Netherlands",
            "Spain"
        ],
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "Which country hosted the FIFA World Cup 2010?",
        "options": [
            "Brazil",
            "South Africa",
            "Russia",
            "Germany"
        ],
        "answer": "South Africa"
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "Who is the top scorer in UEFA Champions League history?",
        "options": [
            "Messi",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Lewandowski",
            "Raúl"
        ],
        "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "Which country is known as 'La Albiceleste'?",
        "options": [
            "Italy",
            "Uruguay",
            "Spain",
            "Argentina"
        ],
        "answer": "Argentina"
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "Which club is nicknamed 'Blaugrana'?",
        "options": [
            "Barcelona",
            "Real Madrid",
            "Bayern Munich",
            "Juventus"
        ],
        "answer": "Barcelona"
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "question": "Who won the FIFA World Cup Golden Boot in 2014?",
        "options": [
            "Messi",
            "James Rodríguez",
            "Thomas Müller",
            "Ronaldo"
        ],
        "answer": "James Rodríguez"
    }
]